[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actress for her role in the 1989 movie The Return of Swamp Thing?", "correct_answer": "Heather Locklear", "incorrect_answers": ["Brigitte Nielsen", "Jane Fonda", "Melanie Griffith"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of the following properties, which is the most expensive in the board game Monopoly (American edition)?", "correct_answer": "Pacific Avenue", "incorrect_answers": ["Kentucky Avenue", "Marvin Gardens", "St. James Place"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food is the Indonesian dish called Klepon?", "correct_answer": "Dessert", "incorrect_answers": ["Soup", "Salad", "Main dish"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the butler put into the cats night-time milk in the animated feature The Aristocats?", "correct_answer": "sleeping pills", "incorrect_answers": ["medicinal herbs", "brandy", "strychnine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Antecubital Fossa is the major vein in the arm for intended vein puncture.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long on average does it take for the suns rays to reach earth?", "correct_answer": "just over 8 minutes", "incorrect_answers": ["just over 8 hours", "just over 80 minutes", "just over 8 seconds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bamboo plants can grow up to 52 inches a day.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The film Grey Gardens premiered at what New York theater?", "correct_answer": "The Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bijou", "The Imperial", "The Berlin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Frank Sinatra write the classic tune Moonlight Becomes You?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was the so-called Dunce hat used in 19th and 20th century?", "correct_answer": "In schools", "incorrect_answers": ["In water sports", "In military", "In hospitals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the mermaid character from Disneys 1989 animated movie The Little Mermaid?", "correct_answer": "Ariel", "incorrect_answers": ["Akasha", "Marina", "Florabelle"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of pet does Napoleons grandmother own and what is its name?", "correct_answer": "a llama named Tina", "incorrect_answers": ["a dog named Boo", "a turtle named Michael", "a parrot named Crackers"]}]